Chicago Ethnic Arts Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 7: Graphic Materials, 1977
  - Subseries 1: Color slides and negatives
    - Scandinavian Americans
      - Svea Restaurant; Norwegian Independence Day Parade, Chicago, Illinois; J. Harry Andersen, Chicago, Illinois; Danish-American Athletic Club, Chicago, Illinois, May 13 - May 14, 1977, May 13, 1977; AFC 1981/004: b44422; Jens Lund; 35 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0a-5, Kurt Mathiasson (with accordion and guitar) and unidentified employees in Svea Restaurant kitchen, 5236 N. Clark, Andersonville (Swedish-American); 0a-2 (Mrs. K.) Solveig Mathiasson (seated, white uniform) (Swedish-American); 5a-16, Norwegian Independence Day Parade, State St., the Loop; 16a, view of 3400 block, N. Oak Park Ave., Jan Harry and Josefa Andersen's house in center (Norwegian-American); 17a, yard ornament of Andersen's neighbor, N. Oak Park Ave.; 18a-20a, in the Andersen home; 18a painting by Per Guldbrandsen; 19a kransekake (marzipan wreath); 20a buffet table; 21a-34, Danish-American Athletic Club, 4624 N. Pulaski Rd.; 23a, cocktail hour table in basement; 24a-32, dinner; 26-28, Mrs. Elisabeth Larsen, right; 28-32, unidentified Swedish-American vocalist; 32a-34, D.A.A.C. bulletin board (Danish-American Athletic Club).
      - Norwegian Independence Day Parade, State St., The Loop, Chicago, Illinois, May 14, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b44423; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Rev. James Callozzo, iconographer, Chicago, Illinois; Norwegian Independence Day Celebration at the home of J. Harry and Josefa Andersen, Chicago, Illinois, May 14, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b44424; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Jovan Michailovic, Chicago, Illinois; Ray Nilsen, Chicago, Illinois, May 15, 1977; May 17, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b44669; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-27, home of Serbian American violinist/painter Jovan Demetrius Mihailovic, 5112 N. Wolcott (Mr. Michailovic wearing dark turtleneck); 25, 27, Greta Swenson, center; 29-37, Ray Nilsen at home, 6039 N. Newberg; 29-30, 37 Jens Lund, left, Ray Nilsen, right; 31-32, exterior of Nilsen home; 30-36, Ray Nilsen.
      - Oplenac Yugoslav Folklore Group, Chicago, Illinois; Continental Night Club, Chicago, Illinois; J. Harry and Josefa Andersen, Chicago, Illinois, June 05 - June 06, 1977, June 05, 1977; AFC 1981/004: b47821; Carl Fleischhauer; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Danish Americans
      - Danish Singing Society Harmonien rehearsing at Normennenes Singing Society Hall, 2414 N. Kedzie Blvd., Logan Square, Chicago, Illinois, June 09, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 074; Carl Fleischhauer; 6 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-6, Danish Singing Society Harmonien rehearsing at Normennenes Singing Society Hall, 2414 N. Kedzie Blvd., Logan Square - Wayne Spies is leading (dark suit, reddish tie, standing in frames 5 and 6).
      - Svea Restaurant; Norwegian Independence Day ParadeChicago, Illinois; J. Harry Andersen, Chicago, Illinois; Danish-American Athletic Club, Chicago, Illinois, June 09, 1977; May 14, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b44422; Jens Lund; 35 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Bandurist Youth Group, Chicago, Illinois; Danish Singing Society; project photographer Jonas Dovydenas, Chicago, Illinois, June 09, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b48714; Carl Fleischhauer; 36 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-4a, solo player in Bandurist Youth Group, the field documentation does not make clear if this is St. Volodymyr Ukrainian Orthodox Cathedral (probably) or Sts Volodymyr and Olha Ukrainian Catholic Church; 5-17, Danish Singing Society Harmonien rehearsing at Normennernes Singing Society Hall, 2414 N. Kedzie Blvd, Logan Square, led by Wayne Spies; 18, Peder Larsen (president), Holger Morch and unidentified listen to playback; 19-27, smorrebrod (o with stroke), Danish sandwiches at banquet in basement after rehearsal; 19-20, Wayne Spies, 2nd from left; Pedar Larsen, far right; 22, Wayne Spies, left; Peder Larsen, 2nd from right; 25, Peder Larsen, left at far end of table; Wayne Spies, far end of right side of table; 26-27a, Peter Larsen, right; 28-35, project photographer Jonas Dovydenas editing pictures at home.
    - Indians of North America
      - Second Annual American Indian Fine Arts, Crafts and Trade Show, Lincoln Park Center, 2520 N. Lincoln Park, Chicago, Illinois, April 28, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 078; Jonas Dovydenas; 10 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-10, unidentified American Indian craftmen and craftswomen with their work at the Second Annual American Indian Fine Arts, Crafts and Trade Show at Lincoln Park Center, 2520 N. Lincoln Park, Chicago.
      - Lyman Pierce, Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center, Chicago, Illinois, August 15, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 079; Jonas Dovydenas; 6 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-6, Lyman Pierce, executive director of the Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center, in front of the American Indian Business Association Industrial Training and Employment Program office, 1124 W. Granville, Chicago.
      - Street Scenes, Chicago, Illinois; Second American Indian Fine Arts, Crafts and Trade Show, Chicago, Illinois, April 30, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b41989; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-20a, scenes of Uptown neighborhood, near Magnolia and Racine; 21-36, second Annual American Indian Fine Arts, Crafts and Trade Show at Lincoln Park Center, 2520 N. Lincoln Park, Chicago, Illinois, unidentified American Indian craft-makers with their work.
      - Second Annual American Indian Fine Arts, Crafts and Trade Show, Lincoln Park Center, 2520 N. Lincoln Park, Chicago, Illinois, April 29, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b41992; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-36, Second Annual American Indian Fine Arts, Crafts and Trade Show at Lincoln Park Center, 2520 N. Lincoln Park, Chicago, Illinois; unidentified American Indian crafts-makers with their work.
      - Second Annual American Indian Fine Arts, Crafts and Trade Show, Lincoln Park Center, 2520 N. Lincoln Park, Chicago, Illinois; Maxwell Street Market, Chicago, Illinois, April 30 - May 01, 1977, April 30, 1977; AFC 1981/004: b42180; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Schmitts Metzgerei, Chicago, Illinois; Second American Indian Fine Arts, Crafts and Trade Show, Lincoln Park Center, 2520 N. Lincoln Park, Chicago, Illinois, April 28, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b43068; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - St. Jerome's Annual Parish Festival; Lyman Pierce, Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center, Chicago, Illinois, August 15, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b72635; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-22, at the St. Jerome Croatian Catholic Church Annual Parish Festival in Bridgeport, site of much Croatian nationalism; 23-36, Lyman Pierce, executive director of the Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center.
      - Lyman Pierce, Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center; Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush artist; Little Village neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b72637; Jonas Dovydenas; 33 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-5, Lyman Pierce, executive director of the Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center, in front of American Indian Business Association Industrial Employment and Training Program office, 1124 W. Granville, Chicago; 6-10, Street scene, Davidson's Bakery; 11-13, Latino mural in the predominantly Mexican American Little Village neighborhood, depicting a rural scene presumably in Mexico; 14-15, Wall mural in the Little Village neighborhood, slogan on mural painted in Spanish ("El Respeto al Derecho Ajeno es La Paz") and English ("To Respect the Rights of Your Neighbor is Peace"), attributed on the mural to Benito Juarez, former president of Mexico; 16-22, Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush painter, with his work, 6244 N. Claremont, Chicago; 23-26, Mr. Park and unidentified children; 27-33, Mr. Park playing bamboo flute.
    - African Americans
      - Quilts, Mrs. Katy Gregory and her daughter, Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 080; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-8, Mrs. Katy Gregory and her daughter, Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson, craftswomen, 335 W. 114th St., Chicago, red, white and blue quilt - unidentified child - possibly a family record, since names and birth dates are embroidered on each square; 9-10, orange, beige, and yellow quilt - medallion type - Mrs. Jackson on left, Beverly Robinson (?) on right; 11-12, multi-color (pastel) quilt; 13-18, unjoined quilt blocks in Dresden plate type pattern - held by Mrs. Jackson, left, Mrs Gregory, right; 19-20, yellow, pink, blue and white quilt held by Mrs. Gregory - Trip Round the World pattern variation.
      - Quilts, Mrs. Katy Gregory and her daughter, Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 081; Jonas Dovydenas; 9 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-9, Sunbonnet Sue quilt, with close-ups of some blocks, at the home of Mrs. Katy Gregory and her daughter, Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson, craftwomen, 335 W. 114th St., Chicago - unidentified child in photos.
      - Home of Mrs. Katy Gregory and her daughter, Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 082; Jonas Dovydenas; 9 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-2, lightbulb figures made by Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson at the home of Mrs. Katy Gregory and her daughter, Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson, craftwomen, 335 W. 114th St., Chicago; 3-9, craft work area and materials.
      - Home of Mrs. Claudia Johnson and her daughter, Mary Young, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois, May 22, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 083; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, dolls made by Mrs. Claudia Johnson and her daughter, Mary Young, craftswomen, 4359 S. Oakenwald, Chicago.
      - Home of Mrs. Claudia Johnson and her daughter, Mary Young, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois, May 22, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 084; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
      - Home of Mrs. Claudia Johnson and her daughter, Mary Young, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois, May 22, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 085; Jonas Dovydenas; 9 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-7, dolls made by Mrs. Claudia Johnson and her daughter, Mary Young, craftswomen, 4359 S. Oakenwald, Chicago; 8-9, red, white, and blue log cabin quilt.
      - Friday night services: McGee Temple, Church of God in Christ, 4946 S. Vincennes, Chicago, Illinois, May 27, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 086; Jonas Dovydenas; 10 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-2, unidentified children with basketball; 3-4, unidentified woman and children on steps of McGee Temple, Church of God in Christ, 4946 S. Vincennes, Chicago, Friday night services; 5-6, interior of the church - slides are very dark; 7-9, wall decorations - painted clouds and angels, portrait, and banner with Biblical quotation; 10, three unidentified men.
      - Kingston Mines Bar, Chicago, Illinois, May 24, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 087; Jonas Dovydenas; 8 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-8, at the Kingston Mines Bar, Louis Myers on guitar, others unidentified.
      - Theresa's Lounge, 4801 South Indiana Ave., Chicago, Illinois, May 25, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 088; Jonas Dovydenas; 16 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-11, exterior of Theresa's Lounge, 48th and Indiana, with Theresa's dog Ship; 12-16, Theresa Needham with fieldworker Ralph Metcalfe, Jr. at bar.
      - James Mack, musician, Chicago, Illinois, May 25, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 089; Jonas Dovydenas; 8 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-6, James Mack, with flute, 1400 E. 55th Place, Chicago; 7-8, James Mack with unidentified female.
      - Grace Jackson, Grace's Garden of Eden, Chicago, Illinois, May 25, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 090; Jonas Dovydenas; 6 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-3, Grace Jackson at Grace's Garden of Eden, a health food store, 6449 King Dr., Chicago, with fieldworker Ralph Metcalfe; 4-5, Grace Jackson; 6, interior of store.
      - The Lefty Dizz Shock Treatment at the Checkerboard Lounge, 423 E. 43rd St., Chicago, Illinois, May 30, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 091; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1- 20, the Lefty Dizz Shock Treatment at the Checkerboard Lounge, 423 E. 43rd, Chicago, musicians: Lefty Dizz, lead guitar and vocal (wearing flowered shirt); Sylvia Embry, bass (loose blue top ), Kevin Donnelly, guitar (white tee shirt); Woody Williams (?), vocal; note: all slides are very dark (underexposed).
      - The Lefty Dizz Shock Treatment at the Checkerboard Lounge, 423 E. 43rd St., Chicago, Illinois, May 30, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 092; Jonas Dovydenas; 11 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-11, the Lefty Dizz Shock Treatment at the Checkerboard Lounge, 423 E. 43rd, Chicago, musicians: Lefty Dizz, lead guitar and vocal (wearing flowered shirt); Sylvia Embry, bass (loose blue top), Kevin Donnelly, guitar (white tee shirt); Woody Williams (?), vocal; note: all slides are very dark (underexposed).
      - Val Grey Ward: Kuumba Workshop, 2222 S. Michigan, Chicago, Illinois, May 27, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 093; Jonas Dovydenas; 9 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-3, fieldworker Ralph Metcalfe, left, interviewing Val Grey Ward, Kuumba Workshop, 2222 S. Michigan, Chicago; 4-9, unidentified actors with Val Grey Ward, in jumper and striped shirt.
      - Yaoundé Olu, uniphysicist, at her Osun Studio, 2541 E. 75th St., Chicago, Illinois, June 10, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 094; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-3, Yaounde Olu, uniphysicist, at her Osun Studio, 2541 E. 75th St., Chicago, outside the gallery; 4-20, Yaounde Olu inside the gallery, with views of various paintings.
      - Yaoundé Olu, uniphysicist, at her Osun Studio, 2541 E. 75th St., Chicago, Illinois, June 10, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 095; Jonas Dovydenas; 4 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-4, Yaounde Olu, uniphysicist, at her Osun Studio, 2541 E. 75th St., Chicago.
      - Darlene Blackburn Dance Troupe, Museum of Science and Industry, Chicago, Illinois, June 11, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 096; Jonas Dovydenas; 18 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-18, unidentified members of the Darlene Blackburn Dance Troupe performing at the Museum of Science and Industry.
      - Darlene Blackburn Dance Troupe, Museum of Science and Industry, Chicago, Illinois, June 11, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 097; Jonas Dovydenas; 12 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-12, unidentified members of the Darlene Blackburn Dance Troupe performing at the Museum of Science and Industry.
      - Jazz Alley, 50th and Langley, Chicago, Illinois, July 10, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 098; Jonas Dovydenas; 18 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-18, street scenes at Jazz Alley, 50th and Langley, Chicago, with unidentified people, signs, wall murals, vendors.
      - Jazz Alley, 50th and Langley, Chicago, Illinois, July 10, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 099; Jonas Dovydenas; 18 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-9, at Jazz Alley, 50th and Langley, Chicago, wall murals; 10-12, neighborhood around Jazz Alley; 13-16, left to right, Charles Hollingsworth, fieldworkers Elena Bradunas and Ralph Metcalfe, Jr.; 17-18, vendor's wares on hood of car.
      - Jazz Alley, 50th and Langley, Chicago; project activities, Chicago, Illinois, July 10, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 100; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-3, at Jazz Alley, 50th and Langley, Chicago, vendor's truck (fruit seller?); 4-11, wall murals; 13-17, hot dog vendor's truck, with customer; 18-20, fieldworker Carl Fleischhauer sweeping up packing materials in photographer Jonas Dovydenas's backyard on N. Kenmore.
      - Maxwell Street Market, Chicago, Illinois, May 01, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b42182; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Mrs. Katy Gregory and Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45142; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-3, Mrs. Katy Gregory (left), with her family; 4-6, Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson with her light bulb crafts (she is Mrs. Gregory's daughter); 7-9, 11-12, Mrs. Gregory, left; 10, House decoration; 13-36, Examples of Mrs. Gregory's quilts.
      - Mrs. Mary Ellen Bowens and Mrs. Elwillie Baylark, craftswomen, Chicago; Jimmy Walker, musician, Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45143; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-1, Mrs. Mary Ellen Bowens, left, Mrs. Elwillie Baylark, right, 6401 South Yale, Chicago; 2-5, Mrs. Bowens, Beverly Robinson (fieldworker), Mrs. Baylark; 6-7, wall decoration; 8-10, Mrs. Mary Ellen Bowens; 11-15, 17-20, 23-29, 33-36, Jimmie Walker (750 E. 46th St., Chicago ) (at piano) with unidentified guitar player; 16, fieldworker Beverly Robinson at far left, Lynn Emmerman (friend of photographer Jonas Dovydenas) at left, others unidentified; 21-22, unidentified guitar player; 30, unidentified musicians; 31-32, Beverly Robinson, left; Lynn Emmerman, right.
      - Mrs. Edith Wilson at the Marina Towers businessman's jam session, "Jazz at Noon," Chicago, Illinois, May 20, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45144; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-15, 18-22, 25-36 Mrs. Edith Wilson, vocalist; Franz Jackson, clarinet; at the Marina Towers businessman's jam session, "Jazz at Noon"; 16-17, unidentified; 23-24, Mrs. Wilson, center.
      - African American craft makers: Katy Gregory and daughter, Ethel Lois Jackson, Mary Ellen Bowens, Lee Ora Crowder, and Elwillie Baylark, Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45145; Jonas Dovydenas; 36 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-2, interior of Mrs. Katy Gregory's home, 335 W. 114th, Chicago; 3-7, Mrs. Ethel Lois Jackson, left; Beverly Robinson, fieldworker, right; 8, Mrs. Gregory, left; Mrs. Jackson, right; 9-10, l-r, Mrs. Gregory, Mrs. Jackson, Beverly Robinson; 11-12, Mrs. Mary Ellen Bowens - she made pillows on back of sofa; 13, Mrs. Bowens, left; Mrs. Lee Ora Crowder, right; 14-23, Mrs. Bowens displaying quilts; Beverly Robinson at right; 24-25, Mrs. Bowens' pillows; 26, sofa upholstery; 27-28 ,Mrs. Lee Ora Crowder, jewelry maker; 28a, wall decoration; 29-36, Mrs. Elwillie Baylark, showing cape she crocheted, 6401 S. Yale, Chicago.
      - Demonstration of Swedish "Halmslojd" (straw work), Chicago, Illinois; Mrs. Edith Wilson at Marina Towers businessman's jam session, "Jazz at Noon," Chicago, Illinois, May 20, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45146; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Jimmy Walker, piano player, Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45149; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-36, rehearsal with Jimmie Walker (750 E. 46th St.,Chicago) and his group, the sax player was from the firehouse across the street; 7-8, unidentified sax player, Beverly Robinson (fieldworker), Lynn Emmerman (friend of photographer Jonas Dovydenas); 9-12, fieldworker Beverly Robinson, Jimmie Walker; 24-25, project photographer Jonas Dovydenas and Lynn Emmerman, center; 30-31, l-r, Beverly Robinson, Jimmie Walker, unidentified guitarist.
      - Mrs. Edith Wilson, Chicago, Illinois; Big Time Sara Streeter, Blues singer, at Elsewhere, Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45150; Jonas Dovydenas; 27 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-20, Mrs. Edith Wilson at her home; 2-9, Mrs. Edith Wilson (5921 Indiana, Chicago) and fieldworker Beverly Robinson holding quilt started by Mrs. Wilson's family in slavery and completed in 1883; 10-16, 20, Mrs. Edith Wilson; 17-19, portraits; 21-22, Big Time Sara Streeter, a blues singer, at Elsewhere; 23-27, Big Time Sara's back up group composed of Sunnyland Slim (piano), Micky Martin, Eddie Taylor, and unidentified bass player.
      - Claudia Johnson and her daughter Mary Young, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois, May 22, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45395; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-15, Examples of dolls made by Claudia Johnson and her daughter, Mary Young; 4359 S. Oakenwald, Chicago; 16-20, Examples of crocheted articles; 21-22, Mary Young, wearing crocheted apron; 23-30, 35, Mrs.Young, left, and Mrs Johnson display quilts; 31-32, Close-up of quilt; 33-34, Mrs.Johnson in front of quilt, Beverly Robinson, fieldworker, right; 36-37, Mrs. Young and fieldworker Beverly Robinson showing quilt.
      - Mrs. Edith Wilson at the Marina Towers businessman's jam session, "Jazz at Noon," Chicago, Illinois; Flying Fox Lounge, Chicago, Illinois, May 20, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45396; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-17, Mrs. Edith Wilson at Marina Towers business man's jam session, "Jazz at Noon," Mrs. Wilson, vocalist, Franz Jackson on sax; 18-21, fieldworker Beverly Robinson, left, Mrs. Wilson, right; 22-25, 31-34, Beverly Robinson, Big Time Sara Streeter, Micky Martin in front of Flying Fox Lounge, 757 W. 69th St., Chicago; 26-30, 35-37, unidentified.
      - Church banquet held at the 69 Club, 117th and Halstead, Chicago, Illinois, May 21, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45397; Jonas Dovydenas; 35 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1 - 9, at the church banquet held at the 69 Club, 117th and Halstead, Evelyn Gaye at piano (back to camera), Donald Gaye (standing) - others unidentified; 10, 15, unidentifed people at banquet; 11-14, Evelyn Gaye at piano, Donald Gaye, vocal; 16-25, Evelyn Gaye at the piano; 26-29, unidentified people at banquet; 30-32, formal portrait of head table; 33-35, Donald Gaye at right, others unidentified.
      - Shape Note Singing Convention, Stranger Home Baptist Church, 1451 W 63rd, Chicago, Illinois; Mary Young, craftswoman, Chicago, Illinois, May 22, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45400; Jonas Dovydenas; 36 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-33, a cappella (shape note) singing convention, Stranger Home Baptist Church, 1451 W. 63rd, Chicago; 34-35, quilt made by Mrs. Mary Young, 4359 S. Oakenwald, Chicago; 36, Crocheted dog by Mrs. Mary Young.
      - Claudia Johnson and her daughter Mary Young, craftswomen, Chicago, Illinois; The Kingston Mines, blues club, Chicago, Illinois, May 22, 1977; May 24, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b45839; Jonas Dovydenas; 35 35 mm black-and-white film negatives